<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vietdoo's blog</title><link>https://vietdoo.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on vietdoo's blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vietdoo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://vietdoo.github.io/page/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vietdoo.github.io/page/about/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Do Quoc Viet, a Data Science major at the University of Science, VNU-HCM. My passion for programming began with competitive programming focused on data structures and algorithms, and has since expanded to Machine Learning and Big Data.
I&amp;rsquo;m deeply focused on Big Data frameworks like Hadoop, Spark, Kafka, and BigQuery. I&amp;rsquo;m always seeking new learning opportunities and have developed skills in C/C++, Python3, SQL, NoSQL, ETLs, Data Warehousing, Visualization, web server technologies, backend development, Linux, Docker, and networking.</description></item><item><title>Review Ngành Khoa học dữ liệu Đại học Khoa Học Tự Nhiên</title><link>https://vietdoo.github.io/blog/review-nganh-khoa-hoc-du-lieu-hcmus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vietdoo.github.io/blog/review-nganh-khoa-hoc-du-lieu-hcmus/</guid><description>Xin chào! Mình là Đỗ Quốc Việt.
Hiện đang học ngành Khoa học dữ liệu (Data Science) khoá K20 trường ĐH Khoa học tự nhiên ĐHQG-TPHCM.
Hôm nay mình viết một bài chia sẻ về ngành cũng như trường, cũng như trải nghiệm 1 năm qua tại HCMUS để cho các em khoá sau có ý định tìm hiểu ngành hay vừa thi đại học xong có thể tham khảo và chọn lựa cho bản thân lựa chọn phù hợp nhất.</description></item><item><title>Rich Content</title><link>https://vietdoo.github.io/blog/rich-content/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vietdoo.github.io/blog/rich-content/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hugo ships with several &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugos-built-in-shortcodes" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a>
for rich content, along with a &lt;a href="https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Privacy Config&lt;/a>
and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="heading">&lt;/h2></description></item></channel></rss>